export default [
	{
		question: "What does Meta-gaming mean?",
		answer: "Mixing IC information with OOC information.",
		answers: [
			"Using hacks.",
			"Mixing IC information with OOC information.",
			"Playing a victim."
		]
	},
	{
		question: "What type of a server is Onset Roleplay?",
		answer: "Heavy RP.",
		answers: [
			"Heavy RP.",
			"Freeroam.",
			"Deathmatch."
		]
	},
	{
		question: "What kind of Roleplay does the server offer?",
		answer: "Text-Based Roleplay.",
		answers: [
			"Text-Based Roleplay.",
			"Voice Roleplay.",
			"Phyiscal Roleplay."
		]
	},
	{
		question: "A Law Enforcement Officer tases you. How should you conduct yourself?",
		answer: "Roleplay the effects of being tased.",
		answers: [
			"Stand up and run.",
			"Roleplay the effects of being tased.",
			"Quit the game to avoid being arrested."
		]
	},
	{
		question: "Someone killed you for an inappropriate reason, what do you do?",
		answer: "Report them to the admins or on forums.",
		answers: [
			"Report them to the admins or on forums.",
			"Run them over.",
			"Kill them."
		]
	},
	{
		question: "Which situation best describes the meaning of Revenge Killing?",
		answer: "Mark is killed by someone, he respawns and kills them because of his anger.",
		answers: [
			"Mark is arrested by a police officer, he spots the police officer off duty and kills him.",
			"Mark is killed by someone, he respawns and kills them because of his anger.",
			"Someone robs Mark, Mark kills him to get his cash back."
		]
	},
    {
		"question": "Someone approaches you with a hand gun in their hand, how will you react?",
		"answer": "Roleplay fear.",
        "answers": [
            "Roleplay fear.",
            "Fight them with your fists.",
            "Run away and bunny hop to avoid getting hit."
        ]
    },
    {
		"question": "You have found a bug that helps you make quick cash, what do you do?",
		"answer": "Report it to the developers.",
        "answers": [
            "Use the bug to become rich.",
            "Report it to the developers.",
            "Tell it to everyone so everyone can get rich."
        ]
    },
    {
		"question": "You were wrongfully banned by an administrator, what will you do?",
		"answer": "Write a ban appeal and make a formal complaint on the administrator.",
        "answers": [
            "Abuse that admin.",
            "Make another account and evade your ban since it you didn't do a mistake.",
            "Write a ban appeal and make a formal complaint on the administrator."
        ]
    },
    {
		"question": "Someone kills you and you kill them after respawing, what would you call this situation?",
		"answer": "Revenge Killing.",
        "answers": [
            "Revenge Killing.",
            "Roleplay.",
            "Deathmatch."
        ]
    },
    {
		"question": "Someone is selling their account which has a lot of money, what will you do?",
		"answer": "Contact the admins regarding the situation.",
        "answers": [
            "Buy the account and use it to your benefit.",
            "Contact the admins regarding the situation.",
            "Do nothing."
        ]
    },
    {
		"question": "What is the proper use of /me?",
		"answer": "/me withdraws a small baggie from his pocket, examining it.",
        "answers": [
            "/me is superman.",
            "/me uses his commands to spawn a vehicle.",
            "/me withdraws a small baggie from his pocket, examining it."
        ]
    },
    {
		"question": "What does PG stand for?",
		"answer": "Power Gaming.",
        "answers": [
            "Pro Gaming.",
            "Power Gaming.",
            "None of the above."
        ]
    },
    {
		"question": "You somehow manage to duplicate your valuable assets, what will you do?",
		"answer": "Contact the admins.",
        "answers": [
            "Contact the admins.",
            "Sell them for your profit.",
            "Give them to your friends."
        ]
    },
    {
		"question": "Someone is breaking a rule, what will you do?",
		"answer": "Report him to the administrators.",
        "answers": [
            "Abuse him.",
            "Report him to the administrators.",
            "You don't care."
        ]
    },
    {
		"question": "What chat command is considered IC?",
		"answer": "/shout",
        "answers": [
            "/b",
            "/shout",
            "/pm"
        ]
    },
    {
		"question": "Someone is insulting you in an OOC chat, what will you do?",
		"answer": "Report them.",
        "answers": [
            "Report them.",
            "Insult them back.",
            "Kill them."
        ]
    },
    {
		"question": "How would you define deathmatching?",
		"answer": "Killing someone without a proper in-character reason.",
        "answers": [
            "Killing someone for fun.",
            "Killing someone without a proper in-character reason.",
            "Killing someone because they robbed you."
        ]
    },
    {
		"question": "What is the defination of power-gaming?",
		"answer": "Doing unrealistic actions.",
        "answers": [
            "Same as meta-gaming.",
            "Doing unrealistic actions.",
            "Insulting others."
        ]
    },
    {
		"question": "Which one of the following names is acceptable?",
		"answer": "Andrew Smith",
        "answers": [
            "Josh B*tch",
            "Tommy Vercetti",
            "Andrew Smith"
        ]
    }
]